Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: I like the multiculturalism. People from all over the world live in the UK and they live together happily. Usually.
Narrator: 2
Speaker 2: For me it’s the language. English is international.
I speak English. You speak English. I’m lucky – I don’t have communication problems.
Narrator: 3
Speaker 3: I like the gardens. I have a small one, but I have flowers and vegetables in it.
When the sun’s out, I sit there and I feel really happy.
Narrator: 4
Speaker 4: I love the freedom. I wear what I want. I say what I want. I do what I want.
Narrator: 5
Speaker 5: One thing I really like is the BBC. I listen to the radio in the morning and I watch TV in the evening.
A lot of programmes are interesting, funny, or educational. Sometimes all three.
Narrator: 6
Speaker 6: I like the pubs. We drink there, and we eat there, too – the food now is very good.
Narrator: 7
Speaker 7: I really like the weather here. It’s cold, but not very cold.
It’s hot, but not very hot. It rains, but it doesn’t rain every day.
Narrator: 8
Speaker 8: I love the Indian food. My boyfriend cooks fantastic curries,
and the UK is great for Indian restaurants!